Guide to the Collected editions of standard authors, ca. 1829-1903.
Collected editions of standard authors
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; “My Novel” on Varieties in English Life vol. III; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1867 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; “My Novel” on Varieties in English Life vol. IV; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1867 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; What Will He Do With It vol. I; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1867 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; What Will He Do With It vol. II; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1867 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; What Will He Do With It vol. III; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1867 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; A Strange Story vol. I; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1865 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; A Strange Story vol. II; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1865 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; Rienzi, The Last of the Roman Tribunes vol. I; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1865 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; Rienzi, The Last of the Roman Tribunes vol. II; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1865 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; Rienzi, The Parisians vol. I; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1874 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; Rienzi, The Parisians vol. II; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1874 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; Kenelm Chillingly, His Adventures and Opinions vol. I; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1873 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; Kenelm Chillingly, His Adventures and Opinions vol. II; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1873 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; Zanoni vol. I; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1865 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; Zanoni vol. II; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1865 (Box 9)
- Bulwer Lytton, Edward; The Last Days of Pompeii vol. II; J.B. Lippincott & Co.; Philadelphia; 1867 (Box 9)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang; The Auto-Biography of Goethe I; Bell & Daldy; London; 1872 (Box 10)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang; The Auto-Biography of Goethe II; Bell & Daldy; London; 1872 (Box 10)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang; Wilhelm Meister’s Apprenticeship; Bell & Daldy; London; 1872 (Box 10)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang; Dramatic Works of Goethe; Bell & Daldy; London; 1872 (Box 10)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang; Novels and Tales of Goethe; Bell & Daldy; London; 1872 (Box 10)
- Amicis, Edmondo de; Morocco: Its People and Places vol. I; Henry T. Coates & Co.; Philadelphia; 1897 (Box 10)
- Amicis, Edmondo de; Morocco: Its People and Places vol. II; Henry T. Coates & Co.; Philadelphia; 1897 (Box 10)
- Cook, Joel; England: Picturesque and Descriptive Reminiscences of Foreign Travel vol. I; Henry T. Coates & Co.; Philadelphia; 1900 (Box 10)
- Cook, Joel; England: Picturesque and Descriptive Reminiscences of Foreign Travel vol. II; Henry T. Coates & Co.; Philadelphia; 1900 (Box 10)
- Amicis, Edmondo de; Holland vol. I; Henry T. Coates & Co.; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 10)
- Amicis, Edmondo de; Holland vol. II; Henry T. Coates & Co.; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 10)
- Lamb, Charles; The Works of Charles Lamb vol I; W.J. Widdleton; New York; 1868 (Box 10)
- Lamb, Charles; The Works of Charles Lamb vol II; W.J. Widdleton; New York; 1868 (Box 10)
- Lamb, Charles; The Works of Charles Lamb vol III; W.J. Widdleton; New York; 1868 (Box 10)
- Lamb, Charles; The Works of Charles Lamb vol IV; W.J. Widdleton; New York; 1868 (Box 10)
- Lamb, Charles; The Works of Charles Lamb vol V; W.J. Widdleton; New York; 1868 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore I; Longman, Brown, Green and Longmans; London; 1854 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore II; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore III; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore IV; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore V; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore VI; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore VII; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore VIII; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore IX; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Moore, Thomas; The Poetical Works of Thomas Moore X; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1953 (Box 10)
- Burns, Robert; The Work of Robert Burns I; James Cochrane and Co.; London; 1834 (Box 10)
- Burns, Robert; The Work of Robert Burns II; James Cochrane and Co.; London; 1834 (Box 10)
- Burns, Robert; The Work of Robert Burns III; James Cochrane and Co.; London; 1834 (Box 10)
- Burns, Robert; The Work of Robert Burns IV; James Cochrane and Co.; London; 1834 (Box 10)
- Burns, Robert; The Work of Robert Burns V; James Cochrane and Co.; London; 1834 (Box 10)
- Burns, Robert; The Work of Robert Burns VI; James Cochrane and Co.; London; 1834 (Box 10)
- Burns, Robert; The Work of Robert Burns VII; James Cochrane and Co.; London; 1834 (Box 10)
- Burns, Robert; The Work of Robert Burns VIII; James Cochrane and Co.; London; 1834 (Box 10)
- Morse, John T., Jr.; Benjamin Franklin; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen I (Box 11)
- Hosmer, James K.; Samuel Adams; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen II (Box 11)
- Tyler, Moses Coit; Patrick Henry; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen III (Box 11)
- Lodge, Henry Cabot; George Washington I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen IV (Box 11)
- Lodge, Henry Cabot; George Washington II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen V (Box 11)
- Morse, John T., Jr.; John Adams; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen VI (Box 11)
- Lodge, Henry Cabot; Alexander Hamilton; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen VII (Box 11)
- Roosevelt, Theodore; Gouverneur Morris; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen VIII (Box 11)
- Pellew, George; John Jay; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen IX (Box 11)
- Magruder, Allan B.; John Marshall; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen X (Box 11)
- Morse, John T., Jr.; Thomas Jefferson; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XI (Box 11)
- Gay, Sydney Howard; James Madison; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XII (Box 11)
- Stevens, John Austin; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XIII (Box 11)
- Gilman, Daniel C.; James Monroe; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XIV (Box 11)
- Morse, John T., Jr.; John Quincy Adams; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XV (Box 11)
- Adams, Henry; John Randolph; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XVI (Box 11)
- Sumner, William Graham; Andrew Jackson; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XVII (Box 11)
- Sheppard, Edward M.; Martin Van Buren; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XVIII (Box 11)
- Schurz, Carl; Henry Clay I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XIX (Box 11)
- Schurz, Carl; Henry Clay II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XX (Box 11)
- Lodge, Henry Cabot; Daniel Webster; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXI (Box 11)
- McLaughlin, Andrew C.; Lewis Cass; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXIV (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; David Copperfield I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1863; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; David Copperfield II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1863; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; David Copperfield III; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1863; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; David Copperfield IV; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1863; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; Our Mutual Friend I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; Our Mutual Friend II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; Our Mutual Friend III; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; Our Mutual Friend IV; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1866; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; The Old Curiosity Shop I; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; The Old Curiosity Shop II; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- Dickens, Charles; The Old Curiosity Shop III; Sheldon and Company; New York; 1865; The Works of Charles Dickens (Box 11)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Abbo-Apul 1; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Aqui-Bart 2; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Bart-Brem 3; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Bren-Byro 4; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Cabl-Chia 5; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Chil-Cove 6; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Cowl-Dekk 7; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Dela-Duma 8; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Duma-Fay 9; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Fede-Fuli 10; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Full-Gree 11; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- The Ridpath Library of Universal Literature vol. Gree-Hawt 12; Avil Printing Company; Philadelphia; 1903 (Box 12)
- Holst, Dr. H. Von; John C. Calhoun; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXII (Box 12)
- Roosevelt, Theodore; Thomas H. Benton; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXIII (Box 12)
- Morse, John T., Jr.; Abraham Lincoln; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXV (Box 12)
- Lothrop, Thorton Kirkland; William Henry Seward; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXVII (Box 12)
- Hart, Albert Bushnell; Salmon Portland Chase; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXVIII (Box 12)
- Adams, Charles Francis; Charles Francis Adams; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXIX (Box 12)
- Storey, Moorfield; Charles Sumner; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXX (Box 12)
- McCall, Samuel W.; Thaddeus Stevens; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXXI (Box 12)
- Smith, Theodore Clarke; General Index; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1899; American Statesmen XXXII (Box 12)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.; The Life of John Dryden; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1834; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol I (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.; Memoirs of Johnathan Swift. D.D.; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1834; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol II (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.; Biographical Memoirs of Eminent Novelists Vol I; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1834; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol III (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.; Biographical Memoirs of Eminent Novelists Vol II; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1834; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol IV (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.; Paul’s Letters to His Kinsfolk; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1839; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol V (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.; Essays on Chivalry, Romance, and The Drama; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1834; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol VI (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.; Provisional Antiquities of Scotland; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1834; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol VII (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol I; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1834; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol VIII (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol II; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol IX (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol III; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol X (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol IV; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol XI (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol V; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol XII (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol VI; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol XIII (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol VII; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol XIV (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol VIII; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol XV (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Life of Napoleon Buonaparte Vol IX; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol XVI (Box 13)
- Sir Walter Scott, Bart.;Periodical Criticism; Robert Cadell; Edinburgh; 1835; The Miscellaneous Prose Works of Sir Walter Scott, Bart. Vol XVII (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; A Float and Ashore: A Sea Tale; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; The Red Rover: A Tale; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; Homeward Bound: On the Chase; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; Jack Tier; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; Miles Wallingford; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; The Ways of the Hour: A Tale; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; The Bravo: A Tale; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; The Oak-Openings; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooper, Fenimore, J.; The Wing-And-Wing; D. Appleton and Company; New York; 1892 (Box 13)
- Sue, Eugene; Pride: One of the Seven Cardinal Sins Vol. I; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; Pride: One of the Seven Cardinal Sins Vol. II; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; Arthur Vol. I; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; Arthur and Indolence: One of the Seven Cardinal Sins Vol. II; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; Envy: One of the Seven Cardinal Sins; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston; 1900 (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; Luxury - Gluttony: Two of the Seven Cardinal Sins; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; Avarice - Anger: Two of the Seven Cardinal Sins; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston; 1899 (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; The Knight of Malta; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston; 1900 (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; The Wandering Jew Vol. I; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; The Wandering Jew Vol. II; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; The Wandering Jew Vol. III; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; The Wandering Jew Vol. IV; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; The Wandering Jew Vol. V; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 14)
- Sue, Eugene; The Wandering Jew Vol. VI; Francis A. Niccolls & Co.; Boston (Box 14)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Anges Pitou Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 15)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Anges Pitou Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 15)
- Dumas, Alexandre; The She-Wolves of Machecoul Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 15)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Memoirs of a Physician Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 15)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Memoirs of a Physician Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 15)
- Dumas, Alexandre; Memoirs of a Physician Vol. III; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1902 (Box 15)
- Parkman, Francis; Pioneers of France in the New World Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1847; The Works of Fancis Parkman Vol. II (Box 15)
- Parkman, Francis; The Jesuits in North America in the Seventeenth Century Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1847; The Works of Fancis Parkman Vol. IV (Box 15)
- Parkman, Francis; La Salle and the Discovery of the Great West Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1847; The Works of Fancis Parkman Vol. V (Box 15)
- Parkman, Francis; La Salle and the Discovery of the Great West Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1847; The Works of Fancis Parkman Vol. VI (Box 15)
- Parkman, Francis; The Old Regime in Canada Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1847; The Works of Fancis Parkman Vol. VII (Box 15)
- Parkman, Francis; The Old Regime in Canada Vol. II; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1847; The Works of Fancis Parkman Vol. VIII (Box 15)
- Parkman, Francis; Count Frontenac and New France Under Louis XIV Vol. I; Little, Brown and Company; Boston; 1847; The Works of Fancis Parkman Vol. IX (Box 15)
- Lowell, James Russell; The Poetical Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. III; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1848; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. IX (Box 15)
- Lowell, James Russell; The Poetical Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. IV; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1848; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. X (Box 15)
- Lowell, James Russell; Latest Literary Essays and Addresses: Old English Dramatists; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1848; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. XI (Box 15)
- Scudder, Horace Elisha; James Russell Lowell: A Biography Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1848; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. XII (Box 15)
- Scudder, Horace Elisha; James Russell Lowell: A Biography Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1848; The Works of James Russell Lowell Vol. XIII (Box 15)
- Whittier, John Greenleaf; The Prose Works of John Greenleaf Whittier Vol. III; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1866; The Works of John Greenleaf Whittier Vol. VII (Box 15)
- Pickard, Samuel T.; Life and Letters of John Greenleaf Whittier Vol. I; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1894; The Works of John Greenleaf Whittier Vol. VIII (Box 15)
- Pickard, Samuel T.; Life and Letters of John Greenleaf Whittier Vol. II; Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1894; The Works of John Greenleaf Whittier Vol. IX (Box 15)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; The Poetical Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow I (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; The Poetical Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow II (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; The Poetical Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. III; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow III (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; The Poetical Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. IV; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow IV (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; The Poetical Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. V; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow V (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; The Poetical Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow Vol. VI; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow VI (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; Outre-Mer and Drift-Wood; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow VII (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; Hyperion and Kavangh; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow VIII (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; The Divine Comedy of Dante Alighieri: Inferno; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow IX (Box 16)
- Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth; The Divine Comedy of Dante Alighieri: Purgatorio; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1886; The Works of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow X (Box 16)
- Macaulay, Lord; The History of England from the Accessions of James the Second Vol. III; Harper & Brothers; New York; 1879 (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; Twice-Told Tales; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1882; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. I (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; Moses from an Old Manse; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1882; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. II (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; The House of the Seven Gables and The Snow Image; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1882; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. III (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; A Wonder-Book, Tanglewood Tales, Grandfather’s Chair; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. IV (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; The Scarlet Letter and The Blithedale Romance; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. V (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; The Marble Faun; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. VI (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; Our Old Home and English Note-Books Vol. I; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. VII (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; Our Old Home and English Note-Books Vol. II; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. VIII (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; Passages from The American Note-Books; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. IX (Box 16)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel; Passages from The French and Italian Note-Books; Houghton, Mifflin and Company; Boston and New York; 1883; The Works of Nathaniel Hawthorne Vol. X (Box 16)